Hey, Pen!
Try to jump over that!
See? That was easy!
That was the easiest thing I've ever done!
Eraser:
Lemme try!
Hunnnruuugh!
Save me, Pen!
- Blocky!
- Firey!
- Match!
- Pencil!
- Bubble!
- Leafy!
Icy!
Revenge!
Everyone:
Ahhhhh!
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Announcer:
Match, Ice Cube, Rocky and Tennis Ball.
Last episode, you four had the lowest scores.
The voters have cast their ballots and chosen
which of the four of you will be eliminated.
OMG, I hope none of them voted for good old Match!
Well, let's find out at Cake at Stake.
Oh, I'm scared!
This time we got 158 votes. I have 10 slices of cake.
OMG. I see you chose, like, fruitcake for the cake.
That is just totally an awful choice!
I mean, why would you do that?!
Match is right. Nobody like fruit cake! Like...
Shush, sheesh
So there are 10 slices.
They represent your safety in the battle.
At least for now. Whoever does not receive
a slice will be eliminated.
Announcer:
The seven of you who did not
fall into the bottom four are all safe.
Now there are only three slices left.
Announcer:
Ice Cube, with only 9 votes, you are safe.
Tennis Ball, even with 34 votes, you are safe.
Yaaayrrr!
There is only one slice of cake left.
I will now show the votes.
No, Match, no! You've been eliminated!
OMG, I know it's so, like, hard,
but you got to keep, like, like, going!
You've got to win this for, like, like, like, like, the both of us!
You murdered her!
No, that was our Laser Powered Teleportation Device.
It teleported Match into the Tiny Loser Chamber.
Oh no, Bubble! What'll we do with Match gone!?
Ooh, I don't know.
- Hey guys, can I be part…
- You know what? Sure. You CAN be part of our alliance.
The more friends the better, right?
Match will sure be angry
when she finds out we replaced her!
Oh, silly, Bubble! We haven't
replaced her, we… substituted her!
People, people. Be quiet.
So as you know, you are the final 10 contestants.
That means you've reached the halfway mark.
Everyone:
Yeah!
You all get a reward.
Another reward? I love rewards!
Announcer:
You each get half of a pair of scissors.
What!? What good is this?
Get it? It's HALF of something that can cut things in HALF.
Because you've all reached the HALFway mark.
Ah, ha, huh…
But your competition is about get larger.
Oh, no, you don't mean…
Oh, yes I do.
Announcer:
Just like there are 10 contestants still in,
there are 10 contestants who've been eliminated.
Announcer:
One will rejoin the game.
Everyone:
Gasp!
So how do I re-enter the game?
Well, you may have noticed that there is a
basket behind each of you.
Announcer:
There is also a large basket filled with loaves of bread.
When this hourglass runs out, whoever has
the most loaves of bread in their individual
basket re-enters the game.
Go.
YAAAAAAAAH!
Errroph!
Flower is ahead with 4 loaves.
Announcer:
Snowball, Coiny, Needle and Match are just behind her.
Yeah! Match, you GOT this!
Yeah!
Pin is now ahead with 5.
Flower at 7.
Announcer:
Snowball beating her at 8.
Golf Ball, Spongy and Woody still at zero.
Now Woody is taking his first dump.
Pin is at 9 now.
Flower and Snowball both at 11.
Ruhh... ruhh.. ruhh.. rrreh!
Woah! Spongy is actually bringing in a
dozen loaves at once! He is now in the lead.
What?! That's crazy!
Oh no! I'm drowning! HERRRR... [mumbles]
Ha, ha!
Needle is at 12.
Match is at 13.
Pin is at 14.
Announcer:
Flower is at 15.
Snowball in the lead with 16. Golf Ball now at 1.
Yeah! Go, Golf Ball!
Time's half up.
Eh, eh...
Ha, ha! Woody's drowning as well.
Hey! Drowning is not funny.
Announcer:
Snowball has 20 loaves.
Flower and Pin both at 18...
Announcer:
...and Needle and Golf Ball are drowning.
Seriously, why are so many people drowning?
It's not quicksand or anything.
Announcer:
Spongy brings in a baker's dozen this time,
raising him to first place.
What? That's crazy!
OMG, Match, go fast! Fast! Fast!
Okay!
Oof!
Woah!
Pin's evil strategy brings her into first.
Announcer:
Flower is in second.
Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
Blehblehblehblehblehblehblehbleh!
Announcer:
Snowball is tied with Pin for the lead.
Pen, Eraser, and Blocky:
Yeah! Go, Snowball!
Time is almost up.
Announcer:
Five...
Four...
Announcer:
Three...
BLEHBLEHBLEHBLEHBLEHBLEH!
Announcer:
Two...
One...
Spongy:
Reaauuuh!
Boop, time's up. Well, Spongy is actually at first.
Yay!
- Pencil: Augh, ew!
- Bubble: Disgusting!
- Ice Cube: Aw!
Welcome back, Spongy.
Moving on,
on this screen, I will display your
scores from highest to lowest.
Yeah, still at the top!
Aww, what about me?
In the Bread Loaf contest, you got 38 loaves of bread,
so your score is 38.
Last episode, our screen was acting strangely.
I think we've got it all figured out now.
Sorry, I forgot. So who is gonna be up for elimination?
Well, at the end of this episode, the 4 people
with the lowest scores will be up for elimination.
Wow, I would not like to fall in to the Bottom 4.
No, you would not. Having said that,
who wants 15 bonus points?
- Firey: Give it to me! I need it! I need it so badly!
- Eraser: Ooooh! Me! ME! Give it to me!
- Pen: ME!
Here's my marble collection.
You'll get 15 points if you manage to
retrieve it in this 10-foot deep vat of hydrochloric acid.
Good thing I have my magnet!
Announcer:
Tennis Ball gets the 15 points.
Yaaaay!
Moving on,
I want to make BFDI as fair as possible.
I think that armless people have a disadvantage,
so they get 10 sympathy points.
- Tennis Ball: Yaaaay!
- Rocky: Bleh!
- Ice Cube: Wow!
- Spongy: Yaaaaay!
Don't even think about it, Eraser.
Time for the 14th contest.
Which is...?
Hey! That's my line!
Announcer:
Jump over the hurdles.
Every hurdle you jump over earns you 5 points.
Go.
Eraser:
Ahhhh!
If you fall like Eraser did, you're out of the challenge.
Oh no! The next one is even higher!
Pen and Firey:
Ahhhh!
So, how is it going, Spongy? Nice to be back?
Yes!
- Spongy: Auuuugh!
- Leafy: Ahhhh!
Oh no! Look at the next one!
Wheeeee!
Alliance power!
[SLOWED DOWN]
- Pencil: Ahhhhh!
- Ice Cube: Ahhhhh!
[SPEEDS UP TO NORMAL SPEED]
Oh no! Look at the next one!
Huah!
Oooh!
Bleheh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh-leh!
Spectacular vomit art.
Oh no! Look at the next one!
That's enough, Bubble...
...although, you may have a point.
Hop!
Okay, I give up.
And that's it. Now let's tally up the scores.
Ice Cube, Leafy, Eraser and Firey,
you have fallen to the bottom 4.
So the voting will only be between the 4 of you.
Ice Cube, Leafy, Eraser, and Firey:
What?
Voters, subscribers, viewers and everyone else out there,
Announcer:
choose who do you think should be
eliminated from the Battle for Dream Island.
[MUFFLED]
Coiny: Pin, do you think they'll ever get us out of here?
Pin: I don't know!
[MUFFLED]
Coiny:
Do you think they'll get us out, Needy?
[MUFFLED]
Needle: DON'T CALL ME NEEDY! BUT NO!
Golf Ball: I disagree! They're definitely gonna get us out!
[MUFFLED]
Woody: [CRYING]
Golf Ball: Shut up, Woody!